(Leonard:)Oh, we have to use the stairs.
(Alfred Hofstadter:)When are they gonna fix
your elevator?
(Leonard:)Uh... I don't... any day now.
(Alfred:)Well, the stairs are fine.
(Alfred:)Besides, your
mother is up there.
(Alfred:)Maybe I'll have a heart attack
and not have to see her.
(Leonard:)Hey, I, I know things
are a little rough
(Leonard:)with you and Mom,
(Leonard:)but I'm really
glad you're here.
(Alfred:)Me, too.
(chuckles)
(Alfred:)I should have never had that
angioplasty because I feel fine.
(Leonard:)Penny's really looking
forward to seeing you.
(Alfred:)Ah, she's a sweetie.
(Alfred:)You got a good one there,
Leonard.
(Leonard:)Thanks, Dad.
(Alfred:)How the hell did you do that?
(celery crunches loudly)